hey there little bit of updates so I
went through cleaned up everything my
whole online presence the best way to
get a hold of me to talk to me to ask me
questions to follow the content is to go
to my GitHub repo I have no other
official landing pages on the internet
right now what is my GitHub repo GitHub
is github.com RBX robob and you'll see
everything is linked from here my Z and
thoughts are here they're now more
polished uh I've started uh several
books which are you know a lot of the
tips and stuff are now in the books you
can get free copies of the books
including a command line assistant to
help you with the books locally um and
you can get you know the other ones so I
went from 256 published repost or
something like that to 10 10 total
public repos and the in fact the main
ones are pinned here so I'm going to
talk about these really quickly and then
I'm going to encourage you to come on in
but if you don't take anything else from
this video just go to github.com
RBX Rob for all the things um all right
so the first one is Bonsai Bonsai is my
command line framework batteries
included it's
here um and it is a very active project
right now probably my most active
project my DOT files which are some of
the most popular things which are all
going to be changed into a bonsai monolo
at some point they they are there the
awesome go page has been cleaned up and
only has the things that are really
truly awesome is there you can go look
at that I did add the pegan
specification the parsing expression
grammar notation if you don't know what
that is it's like Peg abnf and ebnf had
a baby but if you don't know what those
are then you don't care if you do you're
really going to want to care and I'm
going to be doing more work on that in
in the new year um I did added two new
repos I did a books Dash talk and a
books and a boost Dash talk so if you
ask me a question in here especially if
you're a sponsor if you're a Gib sponsor
and you ask a question in either of
these or directly I will answer you
within 6 to eight hours so um I am not
using this is very important I am not
accessing Discord at all anymore I it's
there you guys can go out there and use
it if you want I am not moderating it
I'm not using it at all uh I created a
new slack Channel but it's only going to
be for really really close personal
professional friends that I'll be
personally accepting on invite and uh so
that that means if you if you you know
in slack Channel unless I'm regularly
collaborating with you for a reason
that's really relevant like you know
like Bonsai or something there's really
you're not I'm not going to put people
in that that's not a it's not a general
Community like click on the invite thing
right so I do have a slack Channel but
it's only for like really close
professional peers that I'm working with
all the time um if you want to use
Discord you can use the Discord but you
don't need Discord because you've got
discussions on the boost. talk so
there's three different discussion lists
and these are all linked from up here if
you case you forget right so it says
here so so basically go start and watch
this repo right here click star and
click watch if you want to get
information about what's going on here
on the artex robex Rob site you can
click on discussions and the discussions
are here if you have something nice to
say or want to you have any questions or
anything like that this is where this is
where it is right so but again this this
stuff is related to me so if you have
questions about the stuff that I'm doing
you can put it there um the Discord is
more for the community to share things
between each other um you can generally
do showand tell and all that kind of
stuff on GitHub um as I do the beginner
boost I'm going to be pushing people
more and more towards GitHub and get off
Discord nothing ever good happened on
Discord I I stand by that statement I
think Discord is waste of time most of
the stuff that happens on Discord is not
searchable and you can't you can't get
to it later I I have this problem all
the time with with the IRL stream
Discord they have like really really
important technical information that is
completely unfindable because it's just
this random thread that's out there so
we're going to be stopping that if you
if you want to participate you're going
to need to get on GitHub and this is
where I'm going to go to answer but the
benefit of that is is that I will will
answer you right away on on there as
opposed to um waiting any amount of time
you can you know you can ask other
people on Discord if you want but that
would be fine um there is a slack
Channel as I said and but I'm but I'm
not necessarily using that unless it's
for uh really immediate
collaboration um and then of course
there's the you know comments that you
can put on the chat you can join me for
my live streams you can put um and I'm
generally reading comments on the
YouTube uh videos on occasion as well
going through those so so that's that's
that's a lot of changes
um but please go check those things out
and give it a consideration and uh if
you have any feedback I'm open to the
feedback make sure you know go in there
and create a GI up account and do a
thing um where is the channel to eat
food together that's going to be a
twitch thing so that's on
YouTube uh I've never used slack Beyond
making count yeah well I use slack at
work all the time so a lot of the other
people have been asking for slack who
want to work if the the slack people
very specifically I'll just tell you if
you ask for an invite on slack or I
invite you to come on my slack it's
because I am regularly interacting with
you as a collaborative developer and I
need realtime communication with you
whether it be through you know through
just talking or chatting or huddle they
call it or it's you know I almost all
the communication with everybody else is
the real-time communication is going to
be here it's going to be here during the
beginner boost or it's going to be on my
live streams like right now or it's
going to be you know when I go IRL
streaming or or it's going to be while
I'm uh you know well I already mentioned
the beginner boost so you you know how
to you know how to get a hold of me on
that okay so that's the end of this
video it's a little bit longer than I
wanted but that's how to get a hold of
me that's how things have changed um and
and that's how where you can find all my
information I do hope you'll you'll join
me there love having you we'll see you
soon